



EMILY HOFFMANA Professional Web & Graphic Designer

PROFILE

Reliable, qualified, and experienced graphic designer working mainly in the IT industry, particularly in software houses. Excellence in creativity, problem-solving, time-management, and technical skills. Offering industrial exposure and providing design solutions for a broad range of webmasters and app developers. Works well with the team of graphic designers, and highly participative in business meetings.

Cell: +0 012 3456789

Website: www.yourwebsitehere.com

Email: youremailhere@gmail.com

Address: 123-C. Downtown Road, New York, United States

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (2016 - 2020)

Genetech, United States

I Led a team that focused on providing designs to e-commerce websites. Completed most orders in a 6-month period and won the perfect designer award.

WEB DESIGNER (2014 - 2016)

Comsoft, United States

I worked on testing and improving their websites' designs. Worked with different content management systems and prepared plans for website structure and design.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (2010 - 2014)

Alcop, United States

I created original graphic designs, including images, sketches, and tables. I've built page navigation buttons and search fields.

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (2012 - 2014)

Massachusetts Institute of Technology, United States

The field of my research in the post-graduation degree was "The role of the efficient interface in medical applications."

BACHELORS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (2010 - 2012)

Columbia University, United States

I had 4.0 CGPA in my undergraduate degree. My project got the first position at the international level that helped me won a gold medal.

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop	•
Adobe Illustrator	•
Adobe XD	
Indesign	
Figma / Sketch	
HTML5	
CSS3	

SKILLS

Traveling

Snooker

Video Games

LANGUAGES

English

French

Russian

